One of the key components of humans is our ability to communicate with language.
So it is no surprise that language is being controlled to prevent us from communicating
the messaging of freedom to each other. Germany just banned from protests,
stop genocide, and from the river to the sea we demand equality.
The fact that Jewish people are being censored from apps for speaking about anti-Zionism.
A student was recently suspended for saying free Palestine while their classmate was telling them
they were a terrorist for being Palestinian. What? They're banning pro-Palestine groups on college
campuses and passing legislation to make it against policy on campus to speak in support of
Palestine. A public servant, Rashida Khlaib, was censured for saying from the river to the sea
Palestine shall be free and judiced by her own democratic party but that's another conversation
for another video. But I digress. The fact that people are being accused of wanting Jewish people
to die by simply stating free Palestine, asking for a ceasefire, stating that this is an actual
genocide. I refuse to allow anyone to twist my language into something that is not representative
of who I am and my integrity. Nobody, nobody, nobody who was saying free Palestine, who was saying
ceasefire, who was saying from the river to the sea Palestine should be free, nobody saying that is saying
that they want Jewish people to die. And anyone suggesting that to be the case is being disingenuous
because they know that that's not the case.
What we want is for Palestinians to stop dying, to uphold the government of Israel.
We want the end of a 75-year apartheid regime.
What I know is that language and the ability to communicate with each other has done so much for
peace, for love, and for unity. And right now when you see them suppressing language it lets you know
just how revolutionary it is. So we must not let those who are trying to divide us suppress our
language. It is free Palestine, which is about love, which is about joy, and which is about
equality, which is something that currently does not exist.